epichosts.co.uk 2018-09-04

# EpicHosts - UK's #1 Budget Host :: Get ANYTHING hosted NOW! Games, Websites, Radio Stations, and more!

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which EpicHosts collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User", "You") of the EpicHosts.co.uk ("EpicHosts") website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by EpicHosts.

#### Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

#### Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

#### Web browser cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

#### How we use collected information

EpicHosts may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

###### \- To improve customer service

Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.

###### \- To personalize user experience

We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.

###### \- To improve our Site

We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.

###### \- To process payments

We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.

###### \- To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature

To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.

###### \- To send periodic emails

We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, they may do so by contacting us via our Site.

#### How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

#### Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

#### Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

#### Changes to this privacy policy

EpicHosts has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

#### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

This document was last updated on February 5, 2013.

The Terms & Conditions paragraphed below explains your agreement and the workings of the EpicHosts.co.uk ("EpicHosts") website ("Site"). These Terms & Conditions apply to the site and all products/services offered by EpicHosts. By successfully paying an EpicHosts invoice, therefore placing an order on our site, you oblige that you (each, "Client", "Customer", "Company") are legally bound in agreement to the terms and conditions written below:

#### General Terms & Conditions

EpicHosts is an internet and technology hosting company of which their main purpose is providing the lease of web hosting, VPSes, game servers, radio/voice servers and other virtual products. Our servers are located in UK, France, Germany and Canada, however the choice of country is limited to certain products.

The business is run by ONE individual named Ben Gough ("Terrum"), registered as a sole trader with UK's tax firm; HMRC. At this time EpicHosts does not hire support or sales staff, therefore it is your responsibility to make sure you are communicating with EpicHosts staff only. We recommend checking your address bar to ensure you are only visiting 'epichosts.co.uk' or 'www.epichosts.co.uk' to avoid inaccurate, outdated or potentially fraudlent information along with any form of service we provide. We cannot be held responsible for any impersonators or any result caused by communication with impersonators.

Our security consists of a DDoS mitigation and protection feature provided by CISCO, configured by the datacenter to withstand many various strengths and types of attacks. However, we are not responsible for any damage to your server or services caused by any attack, and we do not provide free backups of our services. Critical data as such should be kept in customers' safety away from our servers to ensure a customer does not lose their data during incidents including but not limited to an attack, outage, corruption or hardware failure. Automatic backups can be provided with our services for an extra cost. We have an automated system in place to block any suspicious incoming/outgoing activity such as port scans, DDoS attacks and more. If we find that your service is sending/receiving abusive packets, your account and/or service(s) may automatically or manually become blocked or suspended/terminated, therefore disallow ANY access to the content or service by the client or visitors for the security of our services and clients. If multiple abusive have been issued, your service may be permanently terminated and any necessary authorities, along with your ISP, may become notified depending on the severity of the issue.

The VPSes we host are unmanaged, unless the Managed VPS addon is purchased alongside with the VPS. Removal of the 'Terrum' account on your VPS, if applicable, is also a breach of our terms and can cause a suspension of your VPS. We require access to VPSes to perform security updates, network changes and other necessary changes that are either requested by the customer or our ISP. The creation of more than one user account per VPS or service is prohibited unless permission given otherwise.

Our web hosting plans are not to be used for storage of data including but not limited to archives, music or videos and should only be used for website hosting content. This is monitored on a scheduled basis and, should we find any incriminating data, you may be contacted or your service automatically suspended. Please refer to the 'Termination and Suspension' section below for more information.

#### Refunds

This genuine host accepts a 7 day money-back guarantee, within reason. If you are not satisfied we may ask for your opinion on improving our services, or encourage you of our true services that you may not have experienced, in case one has misunderstood or became frustrated. We may also use any non-personal information given through any communication method or dispute for training purposes, to help improve our support of hosting and other future purposes.

The decision to whether you are eligible to a refund is always down to the staff of EpicHosts.

The customer is responsible for the understanding of a properly described service, and the necessity of a service. Funds are held with us until a professional agreement is made with the outcome of the refund and/or request.

A surcharge (processing fee) of 7% will be deducted from all refunds and transactions sent from us to a customer due to PayPal refund fees and other potential charges involved during the handling and/or funding of such service(s).

Please note that Renewals, VPSes, Pre-installed services, Dedicated servers/machines, Exchanged services, Domain names and any of the hosting addons/plan-upgrades are non-refundable. This is due to the funds being instantly used to cover the cost and resource used for the process of the appropriate service, this includes, but is not limited to, the fees of setup, reselling, licensing and IP rental. This applies to all cycles except from the 'Every Week' cycle which is refundable only 48 hours after processing.

#### Payment

You acknowledge that should we not receive renewal payment prior to the date of expiry we reserve the right to suspend services immediately without notice. Occasionally we may provide a 7 day grace period whereby we hold your information/data on our servers during suspension/expiration until renewal, but should this not apply to you or should the period expire without payment we reserve the right to purge all information/data pertaining to your account with us.

A service along with any of its data can be destroyed without warning after expiration or during suspension to save resource or recycle stock for processing of future orders. We are entitled to recover (on a full indemnity basis) any costs and charges (including legal costs) incurred in recovering any amounts owed by you to EpicHosts.

Any interlinking services, such as domains linked to web hosting, will be held by us until renewal or a related service has been purchased, as an interlinked service no longer belongs to a customer after expiration of its parent service.

All payment methods are a one-off unless described otherwise (subscriptions, contracts, etc) which are handled by the merchants themselves. Therefore we do not possess the ability to process and/or charge or create transactions from your account - any subscriptions/contracts are an agreement between YOU and the MERCHANT. We cannot be responsible for ANY non-one-off payments that are left unattended or uncancelled as there is no way for EpicHosts staff to acknowledge a cancellation of a subscription/contract without prior notice. A customer must make sure to contact the appropriate payment merchant to cancel or postpone any automated payments before the end of any service's cycle as renewals are strictly non-refundable (See 'Refunds')

#### Server maintenance

We might have, from time to time, to perform maintenance, upgrades or replacements of any hardware/software or content to our services and machines. We reserve the right to suspend access to any service during the required time to perform maintenance, upgrade or exchange the server, allowing us to quickly and safely finish the maintenance without any interruption or interference of a running service. Maintenance usually lasts no longer than a few minutes to a few hours, depending on the severity of the maintenance and whether it is planned or unplanned.

Customers may be informed via e-mail of any planned maintenance. Any unplanned maintenance may be posted on our [Facebook page](https://www.facebook.com/EpicHosts).

#### Setup

It is our responsibility to ensure that any applied hosting package application is completed and activated ready for full use. After completion, all our services are unmanaged unless agreed that managed support will be given. We will not be responsible for any misconfigurations or loss of data due to unauthorised exposure or accidental damage. Re-installations and re-services can be quoted by contacting us for a fee. The customer assumes full responsibility for any third-party software installation and configuration on their service, with no guarantee of support from us for the appointed third-party software. Quoted times for account activation are estimates and, whilst we always do our best to get a service delivered on time, we do not promise activation within the quoted time frame. We may delay or refuse activation if:

\- Stock is being created,  
\- A large queue of orders is undergoing,  
\- Payment is not cleared or received in full,  
\- We believe the order, information or payment is fraudulent,  
\- You have any funds outstanding with relation to your current or any other account,  
\- There is any reason which we deem your transaction as unsatisfactory to our terms or beliefs, of which reasoning would be dislosed with you.

#### Termination and Suspension

You may request to have your hosting terminated (cancelled) at any time by advising us via a method of contact on our site. We will only process a refund if we find it is applicable to the state of your current service(s) with us.

We may suspend any or all of your services, with or without compensation, where we have reason to suspect a violation of our terms and conditions whilst we investigate the suspected violation. We may also suspend your services where we have reason to suspect any type of illegitimate activity including, but not limited to, overdue invoices (lack of payment on any invoice without a notification of cancellation), unlawful content, copyright infringement, payment reversals, unfair usage and services affecting other customers or users on our servers. We reserve the full right to suspend a service at any time with the decision of its final status. You may also be charged an overdue/outstanding 'non-cancellation' fee for any suspended services that do not have a written cancellation logged.

#### Violations

If a customer violates our terms and conditions we may terminate or suspend (temporarily or indefinitely) any services you have with us. In this case no refund will be given for any payments that have been, or are made, by the transactor to us.

#### Changes to our Terms

If we decide to change our terms, we will update them accordingly along with the modification date below. We reserve the full right to make changes to our Terms & Conditions at any time, you also agree that any changes made to the terms are taken place immediately towards all services that you have with us. You agree that you will regularly check back to this page to ensure that you are up-to-date with the latest terms of your agreement.

This document was last updated on March 20, 2018

E-mail: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#f787859e8196948eb792879e949f98848384d99498d9829c)
